http://www.eurima.org/privacy-centre/

Search:
Privacy Centre
EURIMA is committed to protecting privacy of personal data. Our Privacy Centre provides information on how we collect, store and process personal data and allows visitors to exercise their rights in line with the EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
Find out more on how we collect and process personal data
Cookies Policy
You can consult our cookies policy and a full list of cookies used on this website. COOKIES POLICY
Data Protection Notice
Data Protection Notice specific to this site. DATA PROTECTION NOTICE
Your Rights
The EU’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) grants you specific rights to find out more on the personal data we have, to be deleted from our databases, to correct data and to limit the processing of your personal data.
Right to information
Ask us if we hold any of your personal data and how it is processed and the rationale for the data processing. REQUEST INFORMATION
Right to access
Request a copy of the personal data we have in our database. REQUEST INFORMATION
Right to rectification
If you think the personal data we have on record is not up to date or incorrect, you can ask us to correct it. REQUEST RECTIFCATION
Right to withdraw consent
If you would like to withdraw a previously given consent to store your personal data or send you information you can withdraw that consent. WITHDRAW CONSENT
Right to object
If you would like us to keep your personal data on record but no longer process this data (e.g. send you newsletters), please be specific as to what type of processing you object to. SEND A REQUEST
Right to object to automated processing
We do not process personal data automatically.
Right of Erasure
If you would like to be deleted from our database as far as it is in line with other applicable laws you click on the button below. SEND REQUEST
Right for data portability
If you would like your personal data to be transferred to another organisation, we will provide your data in a machine readable format. SEND REQUEST
Questions?
If anything is unclear, please contact us
IMPORTANT
For all requests, please include your full name and e-mail address which will help us in their handling.
If you have a complaint about our use of your information, you can contact the Belgian Privacy Commission. Belgian Privacy Commission Drukpersstraat 35, 1000 Brussels Tel +32 (0)2 274 48 00 commission@privacycommission.be
© Eurima 2018 | Privacy Centre | Cookies Policy | Data Protection Notice
